Kasey Chang

San Francisco, California, 94108 | (415) 413-8249 | kschang77@gmail.com https://linkedin.com/in/kasey-chang | https://github.com/kschang77 | https://kschang77.github.io/portfoliov2

Summary

Multi-phasic Computer Expert with 5+ years of technical support, customer service, application development, and web app development; trained in Data Science, System Administration, Big Data, and full stack webdev; UC Berkeley Extension full-stack web development bootcamp graduate.

Technical Skills

Full stack development with JavaScript ES6* Node.js / React.js / Express.js / Bootstrap / jQuery / Sequelize and ORM / RESTful API / MongoDB and Mongoose / MicroSoft SQL and MySQL / Database development / intermediate Python / Shell scripting (Bash, Cmd) / Regex / HTML / CSS / System Administration / Data Science / Data Analysis / Windows / Linux

Soft Skills

Problem-solving, Communication (verbal and written), Multi-lingual (English, Mandarin Chinese, Cantonese, partial Spanish), Research Skills, Typing Skills (85+ wpm), Writing and Editing, Documentation, Customer Engagement, Adaptability, Analytical abilities, Creativity, Resourcefulness, Curiosity, Helping Others

Education

Bachelor of Science – Electrical and Electronics Engineering with minor in Computer Science

San Francisco State University

Full-stack web development certificate, coding bootcamp, University of California at Berkeley Extension

Google IT Support Specialization Certificate

System administration, cybersecurity, networking, trouble-shooting and debugging https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/professional-cert/9LZTXXTZSDJV

Google IT Automation with Python Certificate

Advanced troubleshooting and debugging, code repositories, scripting with Python https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/professional-cert/NWFAAQPTAHCJ

IBM Customer Engagement Specialist Professional Certificate

Communication skills, personalities, problem solving, and process control https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/verify/U8M8E5Y7YQQB

IBM Data Science Professional Certificate

Data science fundamentals, regression analysis, machine learning and more using Python https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/professional-cert/V53AL32UTWAZ

(continued)

IBM Applied AI Professional Certificate

Artificial intelligence fundamentals, chatbot development, computer vision development https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/professional-cert/TLBXMUHSBR79

Cloudera Modern Big Data Analysis with SQL Specialization

SQL, Big Data, Managing Cloud Storage and Clusters https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/specialization/3ML9NP54B24NIBM

IT Fundamentals for Cybersecurity Specialization

Types of cyber attack and defense, compliance framework and system administration https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/specialization/V6TXWG7PCTKA

Experience

Delivery Driver, Imperfect Produce, San Francisco, July 2018 to January 2020

Deliver up to 100 orders daily from San Francisco hub to all over the Bay Area, door to door

Co-Owner and Office Manager, Ace Xpress Charter, San Francisco, 2010 to 2018

- Managed up to seven buses on the road at one time, and over a dozen drivers
- Maintained all technology in office, printer, scanner, fax, lan, PCs, mobiles, etc.
- Serviced customers from all walks of life, from club parties to scheduled runs

IT Developer, DCL Logistics, Fremont, 2002 to 2010

- Supported over hundred users in two locations of all hardware and software problems
- Administered system as part of IT team and administered database as well on MS SQL Server and Borland Paradox
- Created custom desktop database app that was key to getting and keeping a major client (name-brand hard drive maker), and was used to automate and improve assembly line speed for dozens more clients such as AutoDesk and Symantec, as well as various other database and custom software developments.
- Web development using HTML and Allaire Cold Fusion (CFM) with MS SQL backend

Other Skills

Wrote 200+ articles for Hubpages about variety of topics, from military history to scambusting, still writes multiple blogs as well as ghostwrite blog entries for other commercial blogs.

Edited over 60 game FAQs that on GameFAQs.com alone had cumulatively 2.7 million views (not counting other FAQ websites).

Speaks Mandarin as Native, plus Cantonese, and some Spanish, and of course, English.

Helped expose multiple online scam through diligent research and language skills.

Helping other people daily on Reddit.com as /u/kschang in variety of subjects from writing to programming